xtream-codes.com 2019-03-15

# Xtream Codes

###### *What information do we collect In This WebSite?*

We may ask for some personal information, including your e-mail address, for certain activities on www.xtream-codes.com, such as creating a user account and submitting an order. We may record information about your usage, such as when you use www.xtream-codes.com, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in the Websites (including UI elements, settings, and other information). We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (in comments, in messages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. 

###### *Log Files*

Like many other Web sites, www.xtream-codes.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

###### *How do we protect your information?*

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. However No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information. 

###### *Do we use cookies?*

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

###### *Do we disclose any information to outside parties?*

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include the case when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

###### *Can Children Use Our Services*

The Sites and Services are not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information, including Personal Data, from children or other individuals who are not legally able to use our Sites and Services. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected Personal Data from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete it, unless we are legally obligated to retain such data. Contact us if you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected information from a child under the age of 13.

###### *Credit card details*

No credit card or any kind of financial information is ever stored on our servers. We use PayPal.com one of the most secure and reputable payment processor available. 

###### *What Else Should You Know*

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes to our business, the Sites or Services, or applicable laws. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective as of the published effective date. If the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with 30 days prior notice by posting notice of the change on the “Policy Update” page of our website. We also may notify Users of the change using email or other means.
